When you have recovered from that, there are
also a few other announcements. Do we want to
hear this discussion to the end? We,
Master Shanti Weber,
so hot, powerful,
1000.
But if you get angry at any person, the
body wants more information.
Which combination of the two is an
object's support? It has a special
meaning. On the
one hand, it is the person who
is you. Which of the two is
the person you are angry at?
And G is the person who gets angry.
If you don't know the new language,
you won't understand this.
We should put that in a second truck.
It means
yes,
and
the expression
is not entirely clear,
and even at school it is not
entirely clear whether the person who gets angry is
the person who is angry at you. Until
your budissa price, but I tell you, if
you lose a hundred or a thousand Leones
of good chamber, then
the person you are angry at should definitely
be a few of the author's. If
you lose a hundred million years of good
camera, then at the very least you are worthy of being angry. There are
statements that  If we claim something
we've already discussed, that the
person who is angry wasn't just a
bodyguard but a high-ranking bodyguard,
then they should be a very powerful
bodyguard.
Magma should be the
end of it.
If we
go back logically from here,
then the person we are
angry with should also be a powerful,
powerful police officer. The four
forces and okay,
both the person who is angry and
the people who are
angry, until such a case occurs, that there are such
extreme clashes, that there is so much.
What is she to the body? The person who
gets the anger from the person
he will be. I was in these photos, either
more or 70,
is definitely a person who the
majority also doesn't directly know about.
So, one evening, a normal
person in the sense that
if the state is angry,
they are a powerful bodyguard, but
they haven't yet directly experienced the majority.
If you are politically forcing the
majority directly, so even from just this
one sentence, you can learn something very
important:
you can be a bodyguard and a
bodyguard.  and became a brother,
but you don't necessarily have to have
directly experienced the teaching haid. Is
it true that all people who
have directly experienced the majority
send a tub saddler? We say no.
A very intelligent scientist
who doesn't care about saving the world
can understand that things do
n't come by themselves.
I believe Heisenberg, many, many
physicists have come very close to the majority
without the Potters being Mark
11. Both, as well as, so
both. If you're in the pot, you do
n't have to have
directly seen the teaching haid, and if you
have directly seen the majority, you do
n't have to be a digger. If you were a butter on
the first bully level, then
you must have directly seen the majority. Is there
anyone on the 10 of
these levels who hasn't directly
seen the teaching haid? No. If you
've reached the tub, you've had DP. It has to be that way.
It has to be that way. If you
reach the track, then you're a Buddha.
No,
can you be on the podium, Atrexx, and
not have seen the empty nest yet?
Yes, on the first two levels,
so if  Now it's about the person who gets
angry. It could be someone who did
n't directly know the teacher.
What do you think the bodyguard must be? The person
you're angry at
now has two different
options:
they could be, or they could not be.
So, someone who is a
direct fan, or not. The
person you're angry at... That's why there are
three options in
general. In general, there are three
options. We're not talking
about 1000 or several thousand at the moment. The one who gets
angry is more powerful than the
person they're angry at. The second
option is that the one who gets angry is not as
powerful as the one they're angry at.
And the third option is that they are
equally powerful and have the same
knowledge. Which of the three
is the option that loses 100 of their good
chamber? Again, I repeat
it again: which of the three
loses 100 and which loses 1000? Which one
loses 100? The
bodyguard who
is more powerful and the one who is angry at is
less so. That one loses 100.  Johnen,
and if the less powerful one becomes
angry at the more powerful ones, it
loses 1000. That's how he explains the difference to us.
And what about those that
are equally powerful?
He says now,
but it's called like Adama, the clear view.
But the season uses it here as
obvious. Why does he say it's
obvious? If there are 100 transmitters,
a powerful one that
is angry at a less powerful one, and
if there are 1000, and that's outside, if
the less powerful one
is angry at the powerful one, and with that, it's
obvious, he wants to
express that this is his opinion.
When he says that, he wants to say he
's not 100% sure.
If you say it looks like it's
clear more,
then you're indicating that it's
his own opinion, and so he told
us that this is his opinion.
So if you say that, so if
you say that it's good, the chamber is
destroyed, then it's the second or
third option. But even within the
second option, there are several sub-
options. What does it say here in the
scriptures?
So if you give a lung  You should
use the scriptures,
that's what they say. Even if you
say that's a high lama, if a
high lama says that, then you should
check it or find out for yourself.
Visa and appreciation, but if
he says that, then it's hopeless. If he says you have to find that out yourself,
then he means that
if people later have access to the
sea of ​​scriptures, then maybe they could find out.
If someone
has access to the sea of ​​scriptures, then then
we can make a better decision.
But based on what we
have today, that the decision
will remind you of how we talked about
him going to 100
million planets and beating everyone up.
But if he wants to elaborate on that again,
if in the Federal Council he was
angry at another buddy,
every podium was
injured by another where the seed was,
a bodyguard of the mother in his
spirit becomes angry at someone who hasn't been a
Federal Councillor yet, it's the same as when
he now says that the police
go to 2000 planets and beat everyone there.
He doesn't injure where this  Something
we're trying to say is,
he's trying to explain the
difference between the one who's in
small trouble, who's just
hitting normal people, and the one
under the moderator who's in big
trouble, who gets angry
at someone else where the seed was,
and then they have to put on their armor.
You'll understand life better
when you understand what he's explaining here.
When a bus was sitting,
when he gets angry at each other in his heart,
this has happened, but he doesn't say
anything about it and doesn't just do so
many moments of anger that he carries in his
heart. He carries so many, so many eons,
they have to put their armor back on.
And what do you mean by "they have to
put their armor back on"?
So, if they hit people on the millions of planets,
then
not much happens,
but if he only has the anger in his
heart for a second at someone else,
we have to have anger in our hearts for every second. An "
e" on air is to put it back on.
What does that mean?
And now, another twist,
and maybe we'll die tonight.
I think we really have to finish this.
It's obvious.  In my opinion, it
means that the person is
annoyed,
who hasn't been yet today, and
I was raised Christian. How do
you get water on your head, and then
you're a Christian, and that's how it was. But when
you're 16, then you have to study the Bible,
and when you and then call it
Confirmation,
then you're old enough to be a real
Christian. And in Buddhism, that
means environment, what does it mean?
You've accumulated so much good karma today,
and a brother would come alone
on September 3rd, 2004, you'll be at the
helm.
You've accumulated enough good karma
that the butter can look inside you.
Normally, they do that by
putting the foot on the head, but
we don't do that, and they look at your
chamber and say on December 3rd,
2012,
they will be the one. They can tell you a
date, and if you ask a mother
and say, "Will I be a
miracle?" then look, the gentlemen sit down.
So, it's not entirely clear yet.
Maybe next year I want to reach my
limits, and that means confirmation in the
Buddhist sense. The body is confirmed
on the dual because so far it has
n't been confirmed yet, but even if it's the
other way around, if
you're angry with someone, it
's already confirmed, but the bodyguard who's
angry isn't yet,
and then they tried to prove their dreams,
but it doesn't take long. Now
a bodyguard who isn't confirmed, who's
angry with a mother,
already has the butter date. We can
also do that, outing.
So if the body was sad but still doesn't have a
date on a boat, it's annoying
who already has a date. No matter how many
moments of anger they feel, they have to
put on their new armor twice, finally know what
the armor means. We still know it
nicely, but now tell us that a
beautiful tooth was beautiful, that rail, which
means China
Samad a,
China is written almost the same. The
difference is that the second top
note is a lower tone,
and China means finally.
So, in conclusion, if you ask your breath, it
should...  Bring lunch and
then dinner, then
you finally say, "That won't happen to me,
it's just an example, I get it
once, ten seconds later,
China means here,
here it means we have to start from the beginning,
so they have to start from the beginning,
they have to start from the beginning with their armor." On a
certain Budissa, he was
on the last, on the last stage of
the first five days of accumulation, and when
they are about to get the second stage,
what is the first stage? You have a
drama in your life,
it makes the spiritual dramas good,
and talking about them also came to
China. The first ride, you have a big
drama in your life, your mother
dies in your arms, your brother kills himself
by
shooting himself in the head, and then you
suddenly think, "I think life is
different than I assumed, it's
not all rock 'n' roll."
That's the first part. On the second
ride, someone explained the pen: "If you've come far enough,
then you ca
n't be reborn into the lower enrichment anymore,
so do
n't complain when I explain the pen that it's
in..."  The boat class, the pen, beautiful,
sometimes totally amazing, something you don't
understand, maybe he knows why he does it,
what does it mean? This platform was, was, was, was just about
to reach the second stage,
but then it became very
annoying. On another explosive
point, Lewis Poor's was aware of your need to
move well, and they were ready to
ascend from the first Advent, the second one
found that in the next few days they will have reached
the second stage, but he became
angry. On a bodyguard, it was
with a date.
He pulls out different, too drastic,
the information is hard, but
clear,
if you give up because it has it, then
I can't help you. If you want something
easy, Ingo Andershin,
it's hard.
Other Buddhism is so
advanced that a Buddha
told him the date.
The mobile phone company can briefly say "I hate
you," but really
want to give the anger. It stays for a long time, for
several hours, there. You have to keep it upright,
dancing on continuous anger, because
for so many ions they will not be
able to ascend to the next stage.
Many people always ask me if you don't have any
bad ones.
How can you destroy good seeds? And it
's not that you destroy the seeds,
but it's simply delayed by
several eons. It's postponed
when the next stage is reached,
which is practicing working. Finally,
last week it would have been achieved. You have to go back
and do it again, work again,
and it means there's no need.
He just has to drive back, has to go back to the
beginning, back to square one.
He got angry for
five minutes and two, into a helicopter,
and back to the beginning is worse
than that, and that's the true meaning.
If you destroy your good karma, that
's important. You have to go back to square one. It's still okay.
We're almost at the end. As for the
estimate, the body is almost finished. I have
13 minutes left, and I will
use them. The water level idea was that
if you,
if you get angry, what was still a body
that was very generous in his
life, then for every instance of anger
or that you hate him for so
many millions, you have to
stay in hell. Now, Spielmann, different voter,
estimate, I still have it.  Not
satisfied,
he's still throwing out more
information. We've gone to the sea.
We'll give you the
expression tonight, and you'll see more and
deeper things if he lets.
So what is Master Shanti DB talking about
here?
He says no going back to square one, and several
million years of practicing the first part again.
Now he's talking about the
bright rooms,
and I can put so much good core into practice,
confirmed and not yet fixed.
The annoying thing is to go back to a motivator
with a date of
opening. It's just as
bad to fall into hell.
You can actually
now take it, then he goes to another one.
He quotes another sutra. All
things, all things in the universe ground to dust
with his wisdom, with your
understanding of von der Heydt. It's a to
crysis, the title of a super
in this, so it says there is very
bad karma, which means that you have to give up, and
you've seen it, and
I've seen it too. People
just don't have a difficult time in a
group back then and give up the country name,
and everyone has some kind of
Sorry because I
wasn't wearing anything nice or because I thought
it would be a stupid presentation. What is the
karma for changing your mind later?
And if you do
this bad karma three times a day for seven years,
that's really great. So,
Futter said, if you reject this,
I won't
practice it anymore, I don't like it anymore, and
then you change your mind and say
it was a mistake.
And if you do it every
morning, noon, and night for seven years, and you realize you made
a mistake,
then you can cleanse this karma.
But this person ca
n't
reach the second stage of the path, the one we call patience,
for ten million years. So, the stage
called Shanti, peace.
You don't have to be an animal;
you will be a hungry spirit. So,
within the pen level,
there is definitely bad karma
that you can do,
and if you work really hard with
the four powers,
you can cleanse it. And the second result
is that you
explain to no one for ten million years, you will
always  Yesterday, the sender explained to the pen
that this happened, it happened to
everyone, I have to do something,
so she said to the body,
should we really take care of it, confess,
yes or no, yes, why,
I had to go to hell, will it
fix the delay? He said no, no
matter how often you want, you will, you
have, you were always in the toilet
when the bachelor explained to the pen, you
only ever come when he
asks for donations again, and is the time up?
We still have a project.